

LET'S MEET!

Human resources enthusiast with a passion for new technologies. With 2 years of experience in IT, I've learned creative ways to find the best candidates with almost zero cost and a lot of dedication and self-reliance. I deeply care about the quality and experience we left our potential employees with. That is why I'm really interested in Employer Branding and Nonviolent Communication.

CONTACT

P: 0048 536 399 901 E: gajewska.marika@gmail.com

MARIKA GAJEWSKA-ŚWIĘCICKA

RECRUITING IN IT

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT RECRUITMENT SPECIALIST AND HEADHUNTER Apollogic | 12.2016 - present

- developing, managing and working on full recruitment process
- taking care of company's resource management
- headhunting for internal hiring and external projects
- matching consultants/developers by their skills and abilities with potential projects
- managing and writing resumes for external projects
- filling database with candidate's informations
- employer branding
- keeping good relations with candidates and freelancers
- close cooperation with Team Leaders, Marketing Team and Sales Team
- working of soft skills training for our employes (communication, selfworth)

MANAGER AND EVENT PLANNING SPECIALIST Ironia Cafe&Bar | 2012-2016

- organising events (concerts, party's, shows, art shows and other)
- managing people and their schedule
- looking for artists and keeping good relations with them
- marketing and social media
- taking care of company's documents, licences and permits
- selecting and recruiting employees
- maintaing high quality service

ASSISTANT AND RECEPTIONIST Infosys BPO | 01-08.2012

- office assistance
- meetings organization
- phone and correspondence service
- front desk customer expierence service

RECRUITMENT SPECIALIST

Trenkwalder & Partner | 2011-1.2012

- filling database with candidate's information
- customer service
- lower-level employees recruitment
- contracts and agreements management



PASSIONS

Psychology Sociology Ted Talks Keto diet Minimalism Travels Cats and Dogs

FIND ME:

LinkedIn: marika-gajewska-święcicka/

MARIKA GAJEWSKA-ŚWIĘCICKA

RECRUITING IN IT

RECRUITMENT AND HEADHUNTING INTERNSHIP Ides Consultants Agency | 06-09.2011

- candidate research and screening
- test analysis (IQ, language, psychological)
- managing my own recruiting project from beginning to end

Since 16 years old I worked in many areas not mentioned above. I worked as a waiter, bartender, clothing seller, newspaper seller, pizza maker, nanny.

EDUCATION

PSYCHOLOGY

WSPiA | 2015 - present (IV year)

HUMAN RESOURCE MANAGEMENT

University of Łódź | 2008 - 2013 (without diploma)

MEMBER OF THE STUDENT COUNCIL OF MANAGEMENT DEPARTMENT 2009-2012

SKILLS & TRAININGS

- English | proficient
- Psychological First Aid Training
- IT recruter training | Hopkins University (Coursera)
- Linkedin proficient user effective interviewing strategic screening communicative and assertive | Bee Talents